wutang-corp.com 2019-08-16

# Privacy Policy at Wu-Tang Corp. - The Official Site of the Wu-Tang Clan

**Privacy Policy**  
We take the protection of your data very seriously, so we would like to inform you about the type, the scope and purpose of the personal data we collect and which of this information is used and processed. Furthermore, we would like to inform you about your rights.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact wtc-forum (at) wutang-corp.com or Wu-Tang Corp./Wustore, D21 Residence Atlas, Mohamed VI Avenue, 40000 Marrakech, Morocco.

**What data is collected und processed?**

  * Log data  
When you visit our website or use our forum, the device that you use to access the page automatically transmits log data (connection data) to our servers. Log data includes the IP address of the device that you use to access the website or service, the type of browser you are using, the website you have visited before, your system configuration, and the date and time. The  IP addresses are only stored to the extent necessary to provide our services. Otherwise, the IP addresses are deleted or made anonymous. We store your IP address when visiting our website only to detect and defend against attacks.   
 
  * Cookies   
Cookies are small identifiers that a server stores on the device that you use to access our website or our services. They contain information that can be retrieved when accessing our services, allowing for more efficient and better use of our services.

We use permanent and session cookies to improve our services and the use of certain features on our forum. Session cookies are deleted when you close your web browser. Permanent cookies remain on your device until they are no longer needed to achieve their purpose and are deleted. Cookies are also used to collect statistical information about our website, for example about the number of visitors. 

You can prevent the creation of cookies at any time by configuring your Internet browser and so permanently object the creation of cookies. Cookies that have already been created can be deleted at any time via an Internet browser or other software programs (i.e. Add-ons). This is possible in all common Internet browsers. If you deactivate the creation of cookies your Internet browser not all functions of our website may be fully usable. 

  * Google Analytics: To the extent that this website contains Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (" Google"), your browser may save a password that was created by Google Inc. or third party cookie that allows an analysis of your use of this website. The information collected in this way (including your anonymized IP address) will be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there. Google uses this information to evaluate your use of this website, to compile reports on website activity for website operators and to provide other services related to website activity and internet usage. 

Google may also transfer this information to third parties if required by law or if third parties process this data on behalf of Google. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data stored by Google. You can prevent the installation of cookies. To do this, you must select "do not accept cookies" in your browser settings. Please note that in this case you may not be able to use all functions of this website to the full extent. 

By using this website, you agree to the processing of the data collected about you by Google in the manner and for the purpose described above.

You can prevent Google Analytics from collecting data by downloading the following browser add-on. The browser add-on to disable the Google Analytics Java Script ("ga. js","analytics. js" or "dc. js") allows visitors to a website to prevent their data from being used by Google Analytics. [Download the Browser-Add-On](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de)  to be excluded from the Google Analytics measurement.

  * Google Adwords: The operating company of the services of Google AdWords is Google Inc.. If you reach our website via a Google advert, a conversion cookie will be stored on your browser by Google. A conversion cookie expires after thirty days and is not used for identification. If the conversion cookie has not yet expired, it is used to track whether certain sub-pages have been visited on our website. The conversion cookie allows both us and Google to understand if our visitors came to our website through an AdWords ad and generated revenue.

The data and information collected through the use of the conversion cookie will be used to determine the success or failure of the respective AdWords ad and to help us optimize our AdWords ads for the future. Neither we nor any other Google AdWords advertiser receives any information from Google that could be used to identify our site visitors. No personal data will be transmitted to Google. The IP address we collect will be forwarded to Google only after the data is made anonymous.

You may opt out of Google interest-based advertising. To do this, use the link <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en> and choose the settings you want.   
Additional information and Google's applicable privacy policy can be found at <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

  * Google Remarketing: This is a feature of Google AdWords. The operating company of the services of Google Remarketing is Google Inc.. The integration of Google Remarketing allows us to create user-based advertising and display interest-based ads to our users. Google Remarketing creates a cookie so Google will be able to recognize visitors of our website and if they subsequently accesses websites that are also members of the Google advertising network. With every visit to a website on which the Google Remarketing service has been integrated, your Internet browser automatically identifies itself to Google. No personal data will be transmitted to Google here. The IP address we collect will be forwarded to Google only after the data is made anonymous. You may opt out of Google interest-based advertising. To do this, use the link <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en> and choose the settings you want.  
Additional information and Google's applicable privacy policy can be found at <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>.  
 
  * Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, a third party affiliate marketing network, utilizes cookies to track visits for the purpose of assigning commission on these sales after clicking on a link or ad banner that takes you to the site of one of their merchants. You can read Amazon’s Privacy Policy [here](https://services.amazon.com/content/Privacy_Policy.htm).

**Amazon Affiliate Disclaimer**  
www.wutang-corp.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com. ****
